{
    "subject": "resource/Shahid_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/language",
    "object": "resource/Hindi",
    "human_readable": "The language of the film Shahid is Hindi.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9719817638397217,
            "question": "Is the film Shahid a Hindi film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8770231604576111,
            "question": "What language is the film Shahid in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7935019135475159,
            "question": "Does the film Shahid incorporate any dialogue in languages other than Hindi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7927893400192261,
            "question": "In what language was the film Shahid made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7899065017700195,
            "question": "Could the film Shahid be dubbed into other languages besides Hindi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6025617718696594,
            "question": "What language would subtitles be provided in for audiences who don't speak Hindi and are watching Shahid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5239731073379517,
            "question": "Is the film Shahid a Bollywood production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4973490834236145,
            "question": "Does Shahid primarily use Hindi dialogue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48948946595191956,
            "question": "What language do viewers need to understand to watch Shahid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38647791743278503,
            "question": "What is the primary language used for storytelling in Shahid?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of the film Shahid is Hindi.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2648_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language do viewers need to understand to watch Shahid?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2648_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Shahid primarily use Hindi dialogue?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2648_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the film Shahid a Bollywood production?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2648_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2648_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2648_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2648_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2648_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2648_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2648_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2648_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2648_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2648_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2648_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all three documents mention that the film \"Shahid\" (2012) is a Hindi film, and there is no contradicting information in any of the provided context."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that the film \"Shahid\" is a Hindi language film, with details provided about its director, cast, and language (\"Language: Hindi with English subtitles | Year: 2012 | Country: India\")."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}